Ishanee Kossambe

• 403002 Taleigao, India

in Ishanee Kossambe (©) kossish

ABOUT

I am an energetic student with balanced background in sports and extra-curricular activities. Quick learner with academic abilities and technical knowledge to succeed in different roles. Ready to expand horizons with additional knowledge and abilities gained from training and experience. Always ready to help others and use abilities to support team goals. Reliable and responsible with good communication and relationship-building abilities. Someone who has immense love for the nature.

Education

BACHELORS IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING,

PADRE CONCEICAO COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING 07/2019 | VERNA, INDIA

- CGPA till sem5: 9.01 or 90.1% Is a Member and administrator head of a robotics group called Team BHP.
- Played Table Tennis for the college team.
- Did a 12 week certificate course on cognitive psychology through nptel and scored 85%.
- IDEA GENERATION BOOTCAMP The bootcamp was given by Vocskill director Dr. Artee Aggrawal.
- RPA Programming Workshop RPA Robot Process Automation workshop at Tangentia.
- Attended many workshops and bootcamps.

HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE,

MUSHTIFUND HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL 06/2017 - 04/2019 | CUJIRA, INDIA

- Science (PCMB) graduated with 55%
- Was part of some research programs through school like the mango flowering, identifying roadside plants, mangrove awareness program etc. I helped in collection of data, identification etc.
- Also played Table Tennis for the school team.

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE,

MUSHTIFUND HIGH SCOOL 06/2010 - 03/2017 | PANJIM, INDIA

- Graduated with 83%
- Played for the school in sports like Yoga, Swimming, and Table Tennis, was the team captain for under 17 yoga (5th to 9th standard), for Table Tennis in 8th Standard.
- Participated in many Olympiad exams.

PRIMARY, THE LITTLE PENGUINS SCHOOL

2003 - 2010 | PANJIM, INDIA

- · Completed my education from nursery to 4th standard in Little Penguins School.
- Did a gymnastic course offered by the school for 2 years

EXPERIENCE

ADMINISTRATOR HEAD, TEAM BHP ROBOTIC

05/2020 - present | VERNA, INDIA

 Produced important letters and articles and managed communication with other teams and colleges by corresponding through email. Collaborated closely with other managers to smooth and improve teams operations.

TEAM MEMBER, TEAM BHP ROBOTIC

08/2019 - present | VERNA, INDIA

 Worked collaboratively to complete daily operational tasks against team targets and worked hard learn all required tasks quickly to maximize performance.

BLOGGING

08/2021 - 11/2021

• Created engaging blog posts about the thoughts in a teenagers life while facing mental and social issues and how to work on those issues and ended the topic with small poem in the next post. Monitored content engagement and interaction, tailoring future posts to maximize areas of high interest and improving user experience.

SOCIAL

INDIA

- Participated in an excursion to Mandovi Estuary for mangrove awareness (2018) organized by Mangrove Society of India and made a report on it for the school.
- Attended lectures conducted by Global Shapers Panjim Community Hub on the occasion of Wildlife Week 2020
- Was a member of Kids For Tiger(Jul 2015-May 2017) and participated in different rallies and programs to create awareness about the nature and the endangered species main tigers.

Academic Projects

SHOE STORE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM,

Group Project: worked with Oracle 01/2022

FOOD ORDERING AND BILLING SYSTEM,

Worked with C++ 11/2020

SKILLS

- Strong interpersonal skills
- · Problem-solving
- HTML, CSS and XML
- PADI Certified beginners Scuba diver
- Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator
- Beginners in C++ and Python
- · Database and data mining
- Artificial intelligence and soft computing
- · Cloud Computing
- Languages(English, Konkani, Hindi, Marathi)
- Creative writing like poems, articles blogs

Certificates

SCUBA DIVING

PADI CERTIFIED OPEN WATER BEGININERS COURSE

RPA Programming Workshop

RPA - Robot Process Automation workshop at tangentia

INTRODUCTION TO COGNITIVE PSYCHOLOGY

NPTEL 12 WEEK COURSE SCORED 85%

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Dance
- Travel & Adventure,
- Sporty (yoga, swimming, table tennis, roller skating),
- Music (Guitar, singing),
- Creative (Drawing, illustration, designing, painting, craft, blog writing, poems, photography),
- Psychology